Hi I'm Tyler and this is Marion, a Sulcata tortoise.
我是 Tyler，这是苏卡达陆龟 Marion。
She has dry, scaly skin making her a reptile just like crocodiles, lizards, turtles and snakes.
她有干燥、有鳞片的皮肤，是爬行动物，就像鳄鱼、蜥蜴、海龟和蛇一样。
The grass snake is the UK's longest snake and having scaly skin protects it when moving across rough ground.
草蛇是英国最长的蛇，鳞片皮肤能保护它爬过粗糙的地面。
The adder has brown zigzags running along its skin.
蝰蛇的皮肤上有棕色之字形花纹。
They're also shy and hard to find.
它们也很害羞，很难被发现。
Some reptiles like snakes haven't got any legs whilst other reptiles like sand lizards have four.
有些爬行动物如蛇没有腿，而有些如沙蜥有四条腿。
The common lizard, smooth snake and slow worm can also be found living in the UK and reptiles are found living all over the world.
普通蜥蜴、滑蛇和慢蠕虫也生活在英国，爬行动物遍布世界各地。
The Komodo dragon is the heaviest lizard on earth.
科莫多龙是地球上最重的蜥蜴。
It lives on land.
它生活在陆地上。
Reptiles can also live in the water like turtles.
爬行动物也能像海龟一样生活在水中。
And sometimes both like the green anaconda.
有时两者兼具，比如绿水蟒。
Nearly all reptiles lay eggs.
几乎所有爬行动物都产卵。
They also breathe air like we do, so those who live in water must come up for air.
它们也像我们一样呼吸空气，生活在水中的必须上来换气。
As reptiles are cold-blooded they need to bask in the sun to warm themselves up and be ready for action.
爬行动物是冷血动物，需要在阳光下取暖才能活动。
And if you think reptiles look a bit like dinosaurs that's because dinosaurs were reptiles!
如果你觉得爬行动物有点像恐龙，那是因为恐龙就是爬行动物！
So because Marion is a reptile, that means that she lays eggs, has dry scaly skin, is cold blooded and breathes air.
所以 Marion 是爬行动物：她产卵、有干燥鳞片皮肤、冷血并且呼吸空气。
Oh and there she goes starting to walk off to have a sunbathe and keep warm.
哦，她走开去晒太阳保暖了。